Steven Jackson

Software Engineer

Jalan Mendeka, Labuan F. T., Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia, 87000 | +6087427744

steven.jackson.1989@tutamail.com



A Software Engineer with 10+ years of experience specializing in project management, cloud technology, application development, and Python. A strong history of executing complex projects to design, test, and deliver innovative software solutions to enterprise clients.

Professional Experience

Wednesday Solutions

July 2018 - February 2024

Software Engineer

- Developed and implemented new AI game "Chinese Checkers" using programming languages such as Java, Python, Reinfocement Learning, and C++
- Developed applications and microservices of multi-threaded, high-load (from 2K requests/sec), designing such services, making architectural decisions.
- Designed and optimized databases to improve data storage of offline Android Dictionary efficiency and retrieval speed
- Commercial experience in mobile game development for over 3 years such as "Tank Stars" apk developed in Unity/C#/UDP Game Server

Webby Group

August 2010 - June 2018

Full Stack Developer

- Designed and developed user-friendly interfaces for multiple web applications using HTML,
 CSS, JavaScript and Vue.js.
- Utilized various programming languages such as Python, Ruby, Laravel, Perl and Java to build scalable backend systems for handling large volumes of data
- Manage a team of five developers to design 12 web applications to process, analyze, and render data, including the development of new features to improve data visualization

Education

Computer System Security in Information Technology & Business Technology

April 2006 - May 2010

University Kuala Lumpur, 1016, Jalan Sultan Ismail, 50250 Kuala Lumpur

Key Skills

1C programming, Docker, Django Framework, Golang, 1C-Bitrix, Integral, Vue, REST API, Node.js, ClickHouse, amoCRM, Unity, HTML/CSS/JavaScript, Java/Spring, PHP/CI/Laravel, Linux/Android, MySQL/PostgreSQL/MongoDB/SQLite, Python/PyTorch, MFC/Qt, AutoCAD/Solidworks, ASM/C/C++/C#/VBA/Rust, Perl, Vue.js